Contact



909 Rosa L Parks Blvd #334 Nashville, TN, 37208



(608) 335-9404



frank.a.grullon@gmail.com

Skills

Design patterns and principles



Programming



Very Good

Project management



Adobe Creative Suite



JavaScript, HTML, CSS, React,

Redux, Node.js



Digital graphics creation



Excellent

Full Stack Web Development



Passion for continuous learning



Excellent

Strong communication skills



Exceptional organizational skills



Excellent

Strategic planning



Excellent

Team oversight





Frank **Grullon**

Web Developer

Highly motivated full stack web developer with customer-driven nature and focus on working as part of team. Excellent communicator with ability to meet deadlines and quickly resolve issues. Experienced in project management and web design with knowledge of HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Node, PostgreSQL, and other frameworks and libraries.

Work History

2019-08 -Current

Full Stack Web Developer

Self-employed, Nashville, TN

- Determined coding requirements for site creation, including e-commerce capability and specialized scripts to modernize the 20-year old e-commerce website "Tobita's Crochet Items"
- Used various programming capabilities in HTML, CSS, JS, React, PostgreSQL, and other libraries as needed to create fast, responsive sites and web apps
- Strengthened company brand and identity for "Tobitas Crochet Items" by creating distinctive website and logo - to increase product sales by 20% from 2018

2016-02 -2016-09

Project Manager

906 Studio Architects, Franklin, TN

- Managed teams of architects, designers, and consultants to meet deadlines to deliver quality designs and complete projects in time and within clients' budgets leading to increased company revenue by 10% average per project
- Project leader for complete design and construction administration for Grogan Jewelers' interior fit out in Cool Springs Mall, utilizing efficient workflows and leading to opening 10 days prior to target date
- Created full-scope cost estimates for designed build projects.

2008-05 -2016-01

Project Manager

William Leggio Architect, New York, NY

- Managed all phases of project development including schematic design, construction document production, project bidding, and construction administration for projects ranging in cost from \$400,000 - \$30 million
- Proficient in strong communication skills with clients, project expeditors, building managers, and contractors to meet project goals for over 15 projects per year
- Educated 4-7 key personnel per project in design production methods to achieve expectations and meet quality control standards.

Education

1999-08 -2005-05

Bachelor of Architecture: Architecture

Florida Atlantic University - Boca Raton, FL

Graduated cum laude